American Society for Public Administration (ASPA), Capital District Chapter; Records apap009
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
American Society for Public Administration (ASPA), Empire State Capital Area Chapter Records
1952-1989
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap009
9.5 cubic ft.
Founded to encorage and advance training and professionalism in public administration for New York State
Administrative History
The Empire State Capital Area Chapter of the American Society of Public Administration (ASPA) was organized in 1942 as a discussion group of twenty-five persons to address the lack of professionalism and training in the newly expanded state government. The chapter (known until July 1989 as the Capital District Chapter) was officially chartered on December 5, 1945. The objectives and goals were to foster an "exchange of knowledge and results of experience of persons interested in the field of public administration", "to encourage the collection, compilation and dissemination of information on matters relating to public administration", and "to advance generally the science, processes and art of public administration" [Constitution of the American Society for Public Administration (National Chapter)]. On July 1, 1989, the chapter changed its name to the Empire State Capital Area Chapter in order to distinguish it from other "capital area" chapters and to more accurately define the area it covers.
The chapter was instrumental in creating the Albany Graduate Program in Public Administration in September 1947. The school was originally co-sponsored by Syracuse University and New York University but is now part of Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy, University at Albany, SUNY (hereafter, "SUNYA"). With the help of the Capital District ASPA, an internship program was initiated in 1947 to give practical experience to the newly graduated professionals. In 1950, a trainee program was begun to train people who were already in state service and who were not necessarily studying for graduate degrees.
The national chapter conducts studies and distributes policy statements to 126 local ASPA chapters across the country. These policy statements serve as guides for the local chapters. The chapters do no lobbying; instead, national and local chapters try to improve government through the sponsorship of seminars and workshops. During the 1980s, the society's main area of concentration has been ethics in government.
Scope and Contents
There are few records documenting the early history of this organization (1945-55) due to the lack of a permanent office. The earliest extant records (from 1952) were acquired directly from the Capital District Chapter of ASPA. Most of the other records in the collection were donated by former officers of the Capital District Chapter.
These records show attempts by a prominent group of New York State civil service employees to develop standards for its profession. This group wanted to ensure that professional employees of the state would be equipped to handle the increasingly complex matters of running branches of the civil service. To develop a pool of qualified candidates for civil service, the Capital District Chapter worked on the development of the Albany Graduate Program in Public Administration, which subsequently became the Graduate School of Public Affairs at SUNYA. The minutes of meetings and (to a lesser degree) the correspondence elucidate how the chapter progressed in fulfilling its goals, especially at the state level. The annual reports of the chapter (found in the publications file), compiled by graduate students, detail the issues ASPA was involved with during the year.
The Capital District Chapter of ASPA has helped to improve the administration of state government, and, in conjunction with the national ASPA, beginning in the 1960s and 1970s has tackled such issues as discrimination, handicapped employment in the public sector, and the involvement of women and minorities in government. In the 1980s ASPA worked with the Center for Women in Government, SUNY, to address specific problems involving women in government, such as pay equity for women, equal promotional opportunities, and sexual harassment.
Arrangement of the Collection
Divided into 8 file series.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by the by the Capital District Chapter of ASPA and former officers of the chapter.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Public administration -- Study and teaching.; African Americans -- Civil rights -- New York (State).; Women in the civil service -- New York (State).; People with disabilities -- Civil rights -- New York (State).; Minutes.; Social Activists and Public Advocates; Albany, New York; Public Servants; Maxwell Graduate School of Citizenship and Public Affairs.; American Society of Public Administration.; State University of New York at Albany. Nelson A. Rockefeller School of Government.
- Presidents' Files, 1962; 1964; 1966-1973; 1975-1985; 1; 1.5 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the files of past presidents of the Captital District Chapter of ASPA. At least three of these files--those of George W. Chesbro, Robert P. Kerker and Charlotte O. Gray--appear to have been donated by the presidents themselves. The rest of these files were collected from people other than the president who created the records, but these do seem to be files kept by those presidents. Most of these files are arranged as day files: items within files are in rough chronological order, and contain incoming and outgoing correspondence, meeting minutes, newsletters, announcements, and some notes. For the most part, files under one name contain the records of one president's term, but a few of these files (notably, those for Robert J. Donahue) contain records that overlap with the terms of other presidents and are filed in the presidents' files for the sake of convenience.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Ellis T. Riker, 1962 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 1)
  - Daniel Klepak, 1964 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 2)
  - Morris Schaefer, 1966 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 3)
  - Basil Y. Scott, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 4)
  - Gerald E. Dunn, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 5)
  - Martin Ives, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 6)
  - June Martin, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 7)
  - George W. Chesbro, 1971 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 8)
  - George W. Chesbro, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 9)
  - George W. Chesbro, 1972 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 10)
  - George W. Chesbro, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 11-12)
  - Andrew Krieger, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 13)
  - Douglas R. Martin, 1975 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 14)
  - Douglas R. Martin, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 15)
  - Douglas R. Martin, 1976 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 16)
  - Kathryn F. Minnock, 1976 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 17)
  - Kathryn F. Minnock, 1977; 2 folders (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 18-19)
  - Robert J. Donahue, 1976 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 20)
  - Robert J. Donahue, 1977 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 21)
  - Robert J. Donahue, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 22-23)
  - Robert J. Donahue, 1978 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 24)
  - Eugene K. Tyksinski, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 25)
  - D. David Brandon, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 26)
  - D. David Brandon, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 27)
  - Charlotte O. Gray, 1982 (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 1)
  - Charlotte O. Gray, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 2)
  - Charlotte O. Gray--Awards Committee, 1983; 2 folders (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 3-4)
  - Charlotte O. Gray--Council Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 5)
  - Charlotte O. Gray--Council Meetings, 1983 (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 6)
  - Charlotte O. Gray--Institute Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 7)
  - Charlotte O. Gray--Luncheon Forums, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 8)
  - Charlotte O. Gray--Public Policy Issues Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 9)
  - Charlotte O. Gray--New York State Interagency Information Group, 1982 (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 10)
  - Robert P. Kerker, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 11)
  - Robert P. Kerker, 1984 (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 12)
  - Terence P. Curran, 1984-1985; 4 folders (Box 2 (1-Presidents' Files), Folder 13-16)
  - 60 Years of BPW, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 60th Anniversary, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 60th Anniversary Party Slides, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 65th Anniversary, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A History of the National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs Inc., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - BPW of Schenectady History (1 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - BPW of Schenectady History (2 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - BPW of Schenectady History (3 of 3), 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - BPW Vision, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - BPW Vision Cassette Tape, 1994 (Oversized 1)
  - Club Highlights, 1927-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Club History, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Club History, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Club History, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Club History, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Club History, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Club History, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Club History, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Club History, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Club History, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Club History (1 of 4), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Club History (2 of 4), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Club History (3 of 4), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Club History (4 of 4), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Club History (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Club History (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Club History, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Club History, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Club History, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Club History, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Club History, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Club History, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Club History, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Club History, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Club History, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Club History, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Club History Photographs, Undated; 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Community Projects, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Green Satchel, Undated (Oversized 2)
  - Highlights in the History, 1927-1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - History of BPW Schenectady, 1983-1984; 1987; 1992; 1994; 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - President Caroline Osan's Scrapbook, 1937-1939; 1951; 1962-1963; 1948
  - Scrapbook, 1978-1979 (Oversized 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1979-1980 (Oversized 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Further Equipping Church Leaders Who Oppose the Death Penalty in Kentucky, Draft, 2011 April 13
  - Email from Marian McClure Taylor to Pat Delahanty Regarding Summary of Equipping Project, Attached, 2011 May 2
  - Email from Marian McClure Taylor Regarding the Possibility of Berea Equipping Conference, 2011 May 4
  - The Record Newsletter, Vol. 133 No. 29, 2011 July 28
  - Berea Friends Meeting, Rental Agreement, 2011 September 3
  - Education for Justice, "Respect for Life: CST and the Death Penalty, 2011", 2011 September 26
  - Letter to Catholic Clergy from Pat Delahanty, 2011 October 12
  - Catholic Conference of Kentucky Letter Offering Clergy Education About the Death Penalty, 2011 October 13
  - Pastoral Equipping Event Planning Meeting, 2011 November 14
  - Training for Pastoral Leaders to End the Death Penalty in Kentucky, Registration List, 2011 November 20
  - Constant Contact List for Equipping Pastoral Leaders to Advocate for Abolition, 2011 November 20
  - Event Notes by Don Vish, 2011 December 20
  - Event Notes by Marian McClure, 2011 December 20
  - Letter to Govenor Brownback and Members of the Kansas Legislature, 2012 July 24
  - Death Penalty Information Center "What to Say Messaging from DPIC's Report, "Struck by Lightning," and Results from a Survey of 1500 Registered Voters Nationwide" Presentation, 2011 November
  - Life Matters: The Death Penalty Brochure, 2011
  - Schedule for Equipping Pastoral Leaders to Advocate for Abolition Event, 2011 November 16-2011 November 17
  - Kentucky Council of Churches, Draft Executive Board Roster, 2013-2014
  - Text for Yahoo Group Invitation for Equipping Pastoral Leaders to Advocate for Abolition Event, Unknown
  - "For the Health of the Nation: An Evangelical Call to Civic Responsibility" Document, 2004
  - Kentucky Council of Churches, Executive Board Roster, 2012-2012
- Meeting Minutes, 1959-1960; 1963-1982; 1984-1988; 2; 1 cubic ft.
  This series contains minutes and agendas. The earliest minutes are verbatim transcripts of meetings. These transcripts give a full picture of the discussion held during the meetings but lasted only from 1959 to 1960. The regular minutes from 1961 and 1962 have not survived.
  - Meeting Minutes--Transcripts, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes--Transcripts, 1960 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1963-1967 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1976 (Box 1 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1986; 2 folders (Box 2 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 5-6)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1987; 3 folders (Box 3 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 1-3)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Minutes), Folder 4)
- Subject Files, 1953; 1959-1960; 1963-1989; 3; 4 cubic ft.
  This series contains correspondence, budgets, the records of ASPA conferences (especially the regional conference this chapter held in Albany in 1978), the national and local associations' constitutions, a few publications from organizations with related interests, videotapes of ASPA educational programs (May 1988), and files on subjects they were working on, such as civil service reform. Other records in this series include correspondence that was not a part of the presidents' files or the secretary's files. The bulk of the correspondence is that with the National Association, though much of that consists of memoranda sent to local chapters.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Affirmative Action Advisory Council, 1985-1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Application for the Fred K. Hoehler Chapter Award of the American Society for Public Administration, 1963 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - ASPA Conference in Atlanta, 1977 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - ASPA Conference in Phoenix, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Audit Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Audit Reports, 1982-1985 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Background Summary - ASPA, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Benson, Anne--Director's Files, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Blacks in Government (BIG), 1985 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Budget and Expenses, 1975-1977 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Budget and Expenses, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Budget and Expenses, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Budget and Expenses, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Budget and Expenses, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Budget and Expenses, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - By-Laws and Constitution, 1986 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - By-Laws, ESCAC, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Civil Service Reform--Correspondence and Legislative Acts, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 1986-1989 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Conference on the Impact of Judicial Intervention on State and Local Government Prerogatives, 1980 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Constitution--National, ca. 1988 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Constitution--Revision for Chapter, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Constitution--Revision for National Association, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Constitutions--Chapter's and National's, 1959 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Correspondence and Mailing List, 1978-1982 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence--National Chapter, 1975-1978 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence--National Chapter, 1978-1982 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Correspondence--National Chapter, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Correspondence--National Chapter, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Correspondence--National Chapter, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Economic Development Recommendations for the Capital Region, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Economic Development Strategy for the Capital Region, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Education for Public Administration in New York (Proposed Program), by ASPA, Capital District Chapter, 1953 April (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Election Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - International Personnel Management Association, 1979 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - JMPA Info, vol. 1, no. 1 (Journal of the Albany District Chapter of International, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Personnel Management Association), 1978 November (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Luncheon Program, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Luncheon Program, 1985; 2 folders (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44-45)
  - Membership Development Kit, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Membership Information System Report, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Membership Information, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Membership Lists, 1975/1976; 1978/1979; 1982/1983-1983/1984 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Membership Lists, 1980 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Membership Lists, APSA Officers, 1985-1987 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Membership Reports, 1984 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Membership Reports, 1986 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Membership Survey, 1978 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Membership Survey, 1985 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Membership Survey, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Membership Survey, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Newsletters from National ASPA, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Merit System Report--Change or be Changed, ca. 1976 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - National Conference--1991-Information, 1983; 1985-1986 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - National Council Meeting, 1985 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - National Membership Reports, 1985 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - National Membership Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - National Membership Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - National Young Professionals Forum, 1987-1988 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Newsletter Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - New York State Department of Civil Service, ca. 1985 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - New York State Public Administrators Intern and Trainee Program, 1987 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Nominations, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Office Location, 1986 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Officers, Chapter Council and Committee Chairs, 1987-1988 - 1990-1991 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Past Presidents' Roundtable, 1986-1988 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Portfolio (Vinyl) from Northeast Regional Conference, 1986 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - The President and Executive Management, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Presidents' Plaque, Photographs and Negatives, ca. 1985 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Press Releases, 1986 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Press Releases, 1987 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Press Releases, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Private Sector Affairs, 1985-1987 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - ASPA Publications and Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Public Administration Associates Program, 1985-1987 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Public Relations Materials, 1982; 1985-1988 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Questionnaires on Continuing Education, ca. 1977; 2 folders (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36-37)
  - Rebates from National Association--Petitions, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Regions I/II Annual Conference--Correspondence, 1978; 2 folders (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39-40)
  - Regions I/II Annual Conference--Correspondence after Conference, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Regions I/II Annual Conference--News Releases, 1978 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Regions I/II Annual Conference--Planning Documents, 1978; 3 folders (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43-45)
  - Regions I/II Annual Conference--Summary Reports on Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Regions I/II Annual Conference--Programs and Announcements, 1978 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Regions I/II Annual Conference, 1986; 2 folders (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48-49)
  - Regions I/II Annual Conference at Boston, Folder 1, 1985 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Regions I/II Annual Conference at Boston, Folder 2, 1985 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Sasso, Michael--Election, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Section for Business and Government, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Section for Business and Government, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)